OURI: EYES ON YOU! We are F/ACE!
TAMON: Hello! I'm Tamon Fukuhara.
OURI: Hello! I'm Ouri Sakaguchi.
TAMON: It's been hot every day, but are you
all still alive, my girlfriends?
OURI: Today on our show...
SIGN: Fukuhara & Sakaguchi
Want to Make Shaved Ice!
OURI: we're going to be making shaved ice
to deliver you some chill.
TAMON: Yay!
OURI: Apparently if you melt the ice just
before shaving it, it turns out fluffy.
TAMON: I'll make it all gloopy
and melty with my love.
OURI: This here is called a microwave.
TAMON: Yeah, I know, I know.
OURI: Oh, Tamon-kun.
SIGN: F/ACE Official Channel
SIGN: 1 million subscribers
SIGN: Subscribed
UTAGE: I want to be a trampoline.
TAMON: Yay!
UTAGE: I want to exist as the mechanism
that catapults them to stardom.
TAMON: We're up so high!
OURI: The sky is so close!
TAMON: Lastly, we're gonna top these off
with some fruit.
TAMON: These look really good. Let's try one.
TAMON: Here, open wide!
UTAGE: Romantic fantasies are fun,
but they're just fantasies.
UTAGE: I don't want to be the impurity
that pollutes such a precious space.
OURI: Come on, Tamon-kun.
OURI: We shouldn't be eating just...
OURI: It's good.
UTAGE: So even if he calls me special...
SIGN: Post
SIGN: Tamon
SIGN: Post Settings
SIGN: Tamon-kun trying to dote on
Ouri-kun on today's F/ACE Channel is...
TAMON: You're special, Kinoshita-san.
UTAGE: No, no, no, no. Hang on a second!
UTAGE: That was the necklace
I picked out, right?!
UTAGE: Did he kiss it? Did he actually kiss it!?
UTAGE: Why was he even wearing that
on national TV, anyway?!
UTAGE: And before all that... I mean...
UTAGE: I wonder what exactly he meant
was special and how...
SIGN: Tamon-kun trying to dote
on Ouri-kun on today's F/ACE Channel
is endlessly rewatchable!!
All of humanity needs to subscribe now!!!
#F/ACE
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Amon-tay @tamonuma2525
Tamon-kun trying to dote on Ouri-kun
on today's F/ACE Channel is endlessly
rewatchable!! All of humanity needs
to subscribe now!!!
#F/ACE
SIGN: Post
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Home
SIGN: Favorites
SIGN: Popular
SIGN: News
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Amon-tay @tamonuma2525
The stare into the camera when he said,
"Start, " was just too good!!!
That added 100 years to my life!!
Thank you very much!!
#Tamon #F/ACE #NSta
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Amon-tay @tamonuma2525
No matter what he's doing,
Tamon-kun never forgets about his fans
LYRICS: Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
LYRICS: Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
LYRICS: Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
LYRICS: Smooth as ever, I escort you
LYRICS: And this voice, seducing you
LYRICS: Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
LYRICS: I am your ace darlin'
LYRICS: Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
LYRICS: Please Please
LYRICS: Whisper just to me, call my name
LYRICS: You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
LYRICS: But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
LYRICS: Hey, girl
LYRICS: Look this way!
LYRICS: I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
LYRICS: Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
LYRICS: Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
LYRICS: I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
LYRICS: And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
LYRICS: So take my hand and let's roll
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
LYRICS: It's a spell that makes your heart race
LYRICS: We can't go back
LYRICS: You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
LYRICS: Sweetie honey
LYRICS: Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
TAMON: Your face is
absolutely glowing today, Ouri.
TAMON: No, wait...
SIGN: You're One of Those Insane Fans
TAMON: Your face is glowing
to the max today, Ouri!
TAMON: No, wait. That's not right either.
What am I even saying?
UTAGE: Are you all right?
UTAGE: Working too hard isn't good for you.
TAMON: Sorry, I'm trying to write out
the script for tomorrow's show,
TAMON: and I keep getting stuck.
UTAGE: You write the scripts yourself?!
TAMON: Well, they do prepare a script for us,
but there are free talk sections.
TAMON: If I don't make sure this is solid,
I'm definitely going to break character...
TAMON: So I'm writing a script within a script.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: F/ACE Channel "Fukuhara & Sakaguchi" Location Shoot Script
Audio        Content
Fukuhara: (Free talk)
Fukuhara: (Say whatever you'd like)
Fukuhara: (Poke fun at Ouri-kun)
Fukuhara: (Go with the flow)
UTAGE: Uh, this script seems pretty awful.
TAMON: I end up with Ouri-kun quite a bit, too...
TAMON: I still need to have
a meeting with Ouri-kun...
TAMON: and variety shows are scary... so scary.
UTAGE: So I guess you and Ouri-kun
were just close for the cameras.
TAMON: I'm so sorry for shattering your dreams!
TAMON: The best thing would be for us
to actually get along...
TAMON: But you know how I am. I haven't
opened up to the others very much.
TAMON: I know I'm a jerk for swaying people's
hearts like some kind of con artist!
TAMON: But... There's nothing else
I can do about it!
TAMON: Please just arrest me!
TAMON: Throw me into the slammer
for fake friend crimes!
TAMON: Punish me for not having
the courage to be myself!
UTAGE: I'm so moved!
UTAGE: You've been working this hard behind
the scenes to try to make us fans happy.
UTAGE: And...
UTAGE: Your acting skills are so perfect
that we never have had any doubt!
UTAGE: You truly are amazing!
You're a master of showing us dreams!
UTAGE: Please be proud of that, Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: Whoops, I'll get back to work.
UTAGE: Tonight's dinner will be ginger pork!
UTAGE: Well, I'll see you later.
UTAGE: I guess I'll try out
a new recipe once I get home.
UTAGE: If it's good, maybe Tamon—
UTAGE: Whoa!
UTAGE: I-I'm so sorry. I wasn't watching
where I was going.
OURI: Oh, no. Are you all right?
UTAGE: Huh?
OURI: Are you hurt at all?
UTAGE: Ouri-kun?!
OURI: Please give me your heart, my princess.
UTAGE: Ouri Sakaguchi-kun.
UTAGE: With his clean-cut good looks
and his overflowing privilege,
UTAGE: he's considered F/ACE's prince.
UTAGE: Both of his parents
are famous entertainers,
UTAGE: and he's a thoroughbred who's been in ads
and TV shows since he was in grade school.
UTAGE: He also has a lot of older fans,
UTAGE: making him a popular member
who's right up there with Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: I-It's actually him!
UTAGE: Ouri-kun, please keep your hands
reserved just for Tamon-kun!
UTAGE: I'm so sorry!
OURI: I guess she must be a fan...
UTAGE: Huh?
UTAGE: No way. Where's my homemade fan?
UTAGE: Did I forget it at Tamon-kun's place?!
UTAGE: He's not answering...
OURI: What?! You're not done yet?!
UTAGE: Um, Fukuhara-sama...
UTAGE: How careless!
UTAGE: What if some crazy fan like me
just waltzed into your place?!
TAMON: I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
OURI: Man, you seriously suck
at everything you do.
TAMON: Yes, I am absolute trash.
OURI: Quit giving me excuses!
Man, you piss me off!
OURI: Just shut up and write already!
TAMON: Yesh, sir!
SIGN: Stalker Break In!
OURI: Hey, what's taking so long,
you damn slowpoke?!
OURI: I'm exhausted from the shoot today,
OURI: but I was kind enough
to come check on you!
OURI: Do you understand that? Huh?!
TAMON: I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry, kind Ouri-kun!
OURI: Finish it up in a minute!
UTAGE: Whut?
OURI: Wow, it sure is hot today!
OURI: Make sure you don't
work too hard, Tamon-kun.
OURI: Oh? We bumped into each other
earlier, didn't we?
OURI: Did you follow me here?
OURI: Oh, you must be looking for this.
OURI: This is such a lovely fan. So please
be careful not to drop it again!
OURI: Huh? Did it look like we were arguing?
OURI: We're together every day,
OURI: so we do get into little spats
now and then, right, Tamon-kun?
TAMON: Huh? Uh, I...
TAMON: Oh, you! You're surprisingly
a little troublemaker sometimes, Ouri!
TAMON: You little stinker.
OURI: I just get so worked up
when I'm with you, Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
UTAGE: You were smacking him.
UTAGE: With this fan that's meant
to worship Tamon-kun...
UTAGE: You took it to his head...
and went thwack! Thwack!
SIGN: Unconditional love for Tamon Fukuhara
UTAGE: That is unforgivable... Unbelievable!
UTAGE: I can't believe you...
h-h-h-hit Tamon-kun.
TAMON: Kinoshita-san, please calm down.
I'm totally fine.
OURI: What? You're not even my fan?
OURI: Hey!
OURI: That hurts! Lemme go!
UTAGE: Do not strike our god's sacred scalp!
UTAGE: Farewell!
UTAGE: Are you all right?!
UTAGE: Your scalp's already damaged
from all the bleaching! No more!
TAMON: My skin's the one thing that's tough,
so I'm fine.
TAMON: And...
TAMON: Ouri-kun is always like that,
so I'm used to it.
UTAGE: Don't get used to that!
TAMON: I'm sorry. Oh...
TAMON: Our meeting about tomorrow...
UTAGE: Ah.
OURI: You've got some nerve
throwing me out like that.
OURI: You've definitely caught my interest.
OURI: As if that'd ever happen, you dumbass!
OURI: Apologize, damn it!
TAMON: I'm so sorry!
OURI: Why the hell are you apologizing?!
TAMON: This is all my fault.
TAMON: I'll get blacklisted and blackballed
for ruining tomorrow's shoot!
TAMON: In 30 years, my shady business will fail
and I'll make the news! Sorry in advance!
UTAGE: So what if you ruin the shoot?
UTAGE: Don't forget that you're able to
influence a whole economy
UTAGE: just by standing in place!
SIGN: So bad that it became a hit
Tamon Fukuhara
Standing Stiff Acrylic Stand
OURI: Hey, don't ignore me!
OURI: Who the hell are you?
UTAGE: I'm Gloomyha... no.
UTAGE: I'm Fukuhara-san's housekeeper.
OURI: So you're just a housekeeper.
OURI: Heck, even fans don't walk around
with a fan like that.
OURI: I don't really need to guess.
You're one of those insane fans.
UTAGE: Sure am.
OURI: What's so good about this?
SIGN: Shake
Quiver
OURI: He's completely different
from his public persona.
OURI: Even in this situation,
he's just some quivering loser.
OURI: Seriously... it makes me sick
that a guy like this is our center.
UTAGE: What are you talking about?
UTAGE: Wherever Tamon-kun is standing
is literally the center of the world.
UTAGE: It doesn't matter if he's
sexy and wild or a loser.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun is Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Wherever Tamon-kun is standing
is the Earth's axis.
SIGN: Tamon's idea
SIGN: Earth's axis
SIGN: Day
SIGN: Night
UTAGE: The North Pole is Gloomyhara-san.
UTAGE: The South Pole is Hottiehara-kun.
OURI: What are you even talking about?!
OURI: So you don't even care
about his personality?
OURI: There're always people like you.
OURI: The asskissers who just keep smiling
no matter who they're dealing with.
OURI: They don't even have a sliver of pride.
OURI: They're absolute pieces of shit.
UTAGE: What?!
TAMON: Ta...
TAMON: "Tamon-kun is God!"
OURI: What?
TAMON: Kinoshita-san isn't like that!
TAMON: She doesn't care
if people think she's insane.
TAMON: She's truly a kind and brave person
who can get mad for the sake of others.
TAMON: She's nothing like
the people you're talking about!
FUJITA: Damn it, Ouri! How many times do
I have to tell you not to break things?!
FUJITA: What do we do about this door?!
OURI: Shut up! It's not my fault!
FUJITA: Have some bubble tea and calm down.
TAMON: I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
TAMON: I'm awful at opening up my heart,
TAMON: yet my home's door is so open
it doesn't exist anymore. I'm so sorry.
SIGN: Tamon-kun,
please work
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: F/ACE Channel "Fukuhara & Sakaguchi" Location Shoot Script
Audio        Content
Fukuhara: (Free talk)
Fukuhara: (Say whatever you'd like)
Fukuhara: (Poke fun at Ouri-kun)
Fukuhara: (Go with the flow)
UTAGE: Well, I'll be going now, but...
TAMON: Right. Thank you
for everything you did today.
TAMON: Will you really be okay being alone with
someone that clearly is lacking calcium?
TAMON: Well, it looks like Ouri-kun
is going home now, too.
UTAGE: Well, that's a relief.
TAMON: Um, Kinoshita-san...
UTAGE: Yes?
TAMON: It's nothing.
UTAGE: Okay, see you.
TAMON: I'll do my best at tomorrow's shoot,
so please watch.
UTAGE: Yes! Of course!
UTAGE: I need to keep making
as much money as possible
UTAGE: for the sake of Tamon-kun's future, too!
OURI: Hey!
UTAGE: What is it?
OURI: Don't you dare tell a soul
about what you saw today.
UTAGE: If you're talking about your
true nature, I won't tell anyone.
OURI: What do you want?
UTAGE: What?
OURI: To ensure you'll keep your mouth shut.
UTAGE: I just told you that I won't tell anyone.
OURI: Well, I don't trust you.
OURI: You want me to make him do things for you?
OURI: He'll do whatever I tell him t—
OURI: Ow!
UTAGE: Insult Tamon-kun one more time,
and your life ends right now.
OURI: H-How the hell is she so strong?
UTAGE: Just please tell him
to live happy and healthy.
UTAGE: Also, since you're so worried
about your true nature...
UTAGE: I couldn't care less
about people I dislike.
UTAGE: Not only will I not tell a soul,
I won't ever speak of you again.
UTAGE: So please don't worry.
UTAGE: Goodbye.
TEACHER: Summer vacation starts tomorrow,
but don't have too much fun out there!
STUDENTS: Yes, ma'am!
UTAGE: Tamon-kun, I'm sure it's awful
to have an enemy so close by,
UTAGE: but don't let it get you down.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Home
SIGN: Favorites
SIGN: Popular
SIGN: News
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Amon-tay @tamonuma2525
SIGN: No matter what anyone says, Tamon-kun
SIGN: is always at the center of our hearts.
SIGN: Tamon-kun is the absolute center
SIGN: #Tamon-kunIsAGod
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Gyapaful TV
SIGN: F/ACE Official Channel
SIGN: This Is F/ACE's Next Step to Get to Greater Heights
UTAGE: An update from F/ACE's official account!
UTAGE: I wonder what it is.
NATSUKI: Huh? You're shooting?
NATSUKI: Why so out of the blue?
TAMON: A new song? Heck yeah!
KEITO: A ballad, huh?
NATSUKI: It's so good.
OURI: But this is completely different
from our other songs.
TAMON: This is a first for a lead song.
OURI: So it's a heartbreak song...
TAMON: So sad...
SIGN: We will be selecting a new center with this song
ALL: What?!
UTAGE: Huh?
OURI: But Tamon-kun's supposed to be
the permanent center of F/ACE.
SIGN: "Center"
SIGN: A special position reserved for only
those with immense talent and popularity
NARRATOR: Center.
NARRATOR: A special position reserved for only
those with immense talent and popularity.
NARRATOR: The group's face.
SIGN: The group's
SIGN: Face
TAMON: Bring it on.
TAMON: Acting cool isn't
the only part of our job.
TAMON: Come at me with everything you've got.
SIGN: Streaming live exclusively on Gyapaful TV
SIGN: 5 episodes total
SIGN: Updated every Wednesday starting on 7/22
NARRATOR: Streaming live exclusively on Gyapaful TV.
NARRATOR: A total of five episodes. Updated
every Wednesday starting July 22nd.
UTAGE: Wh-Wh-Wha...
UTAGE: Wha...
UTAGE: What do you mean?!
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san!
UTAGE: I saw the commercial for your new show!
UTAGE: I firmly believe that
there's absolutely no reason
UTAGE: for them to have to
choose another center!
UTAGE: You guys were saying a bunch
of things like how it's a ballad
UTAGE: or it's different from
your usual up-tempo songs...
UTAGE: But starting a project like this
just because of that
UTAGE: is just so incredibly rude
toward you, Tamon-kun!
TAMON: P-Please calm down, Kinoshita-san.
TAMON: Um... Ouri-kun's been wanting to be
the center for quite some time now...
TAMON: So that's why we're doing this project.
UTAGE: What?!
TAMON: Ouri-kun's both popular and talented,
TAMON: so I think he's the right fit
for the center.
UTAGE: But...
OURI: I can't imagine Tamon-kun
not being our center!
OURI: Heh.
UTAGE: That little...
TAMON: I... don't have much confidence,
TAMON: so I can't really blame anyone
if I'm not chosen...
TAMON: Whoa!
UTAGE: Your fans...
UTAGE: We will be there to support you
no matter where you're singing from.
UTAGE: But... You want to make everyone
in the world smile, don't you?
UTAGE: So you shouldn't be
giving up now, should you?!
TAMON: H-Honestly...
UTAGE: Yes?
TAMON: The day... this project was decided...
SIGN: Shake
UTAGE: Yes?
TAMON: I was so frustrated that I cried
into my pillow until it was sopping wet!
UTAGE: I love you.
RIKO: It's summer vacation.
RIKO: And the world seems to be excited
for festivals, beach trips, or whatever...
RIKO: But that doesn't apply to us.
RIKO: We all know that, right?
YUINA: The special program to pick
a new center for F/ACE...
UTAGE: The first episode airs tonight.
SIGN: Is
this
thing
rigged?!
SIGN: Huh?
SIGN: Is
this
thing
rigged?!
SIGN: We're
not
going
to
let
you
get
away
with
this!
SIGN: Is
this
thing
rigged?!
UTAGE BG: Is this thing rigged?
UTAGE BG: Huuuuh?
UTAGE BG: We're not going to
let you get away with this!
UTAGE BG: Is this thing rigged?!
UTAGE: If Tamon-kun gets judged unfairly,
UTAGE: I'm pretty sure I might arm myself
and attack their agency.
UTAGE: I have no idea what I might
be capable of... I'm so scared.
RIKO: In order to make sure we are
able to calmly watch this show,
RIKO: let's review exactly who F/ACE is.
RIKO: First, we have the current center,
our beloved Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Insanely hot standing up,
insanely hot sitting down.
UTAGE: He's literally just a god when he walks.
SIGN: The sexy & wild one
SIGN: Member color: Red
RIKO: Next up, is the leader,
Keito Tachibana-kun.
YUINA: He's the approachable one
you can imagine actually dating.
SIGN: The relaxing one
SIGN: Member color: Green
RIKO: What about Natsuki Ishibashi-kun?
SIGN: The angel
SIGN: Member color: Yellow
YUINA: He's the cunningly cute type of pro idol.
RIKO: Then what about Rintaro Kai-kun?
UTAGE: He seems really mature and mysterious.
SIGN: The cool one
SIGN: Member color: Purple
RIKO: And then we have the projected winner
of this race, Ouri Sakaguchi-kun.
SIGN: The prince
SIGN: Member color: Blue
YUINA: His strengths are
how frail and sensitive he is.
YUINA: He's voted the celebrity most likely to
get whooshed away by cherry blossoms.
UTAGE: Pretty sure they meant he'd go
rip out a cherry blossom tree.
YUINA: There were definitely some Ouri fans
YUINA: that didn't like that Tamon-kun's
been the permanent center.
RIKO: Back then, Tamon-kun managed
to take first place in an upset...
RIKO: But everyone kept saying Ouri-kun
was a shoo-in at the beginning.
UTAGE: Hey, look!
UTAGE: It's starting!
RIKO: Okay, girls. Let's focus!
RIKO: Sharpen your vision!
YUINA/UTAGE: Of course!
SHIRAISHI: The title of the new song is "RAIN."
SHIRAISHI: It takes the regrets a man feels when
he realizes the weight of what he's lost
SHIRAISHI: and turns it into a lyrical melody...
a ballad about heartbreak.
SHIRAISHI: And for the first episode...
SHIRAISHI: We will be having a visual battle
where the theme is "heartache."
SIGN: Heartache!!!
SHIRAISHI: Who can best express
the sentimental feelings from the song?
SIGN: Singing Expert
SIGN: Dance Expert
SHIRAISHI: We will be judging using a point system.
SHIRAISHI: Our first one up is Ouri Sakaguchi.
SHIRAISHI: Use this short script
to express the utmost heartache.
SHIRAISHI: Are you ready?
OURI: Yes.
OURI: Don't go...
GIRLS: Oh... the heartache!
ACTING EXPERT: The rain drizzling down in the sunset...
ACTING EXPERT: Cherry blossoms that
won't be seen again until next year.
SIGN LEFT TO RIGHT: Producer
SIGN: Dance Expert
SIGN: Singing Expert
SINGING EXPERT: The night wind brushing
against his cheek...
SINGING EXPERT: The cicadas' cries being
absorbed into the rocks!
DANCE EXPERT: So this is the legendary happy meal
of sentimentality?
SHIRAISHI: Well done.
UTAGE: Everyone stay calm.
UTAGE: I feel bad for Ouri-kun for saying this,
but this didn't go beyond my expectations.
UTAGE: The one who'll surpass our expectations...
UTAGE: Yes, it's always Tamon-kun.
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's going to pull this off!
So that everyone in the world can smile!
YUINA: Yeah!
RIKO: You're right!
TAMON: Don't go.
TAMON: Don't go!
UTAGE NARRATION: I gained notoriety and praise.
UTAGE NARRATION: I'm insanely hot and an amazing dancer.
UTAGE NARRATION: I could have any girl I want...
UTAGE NARRATION: So why don't I ever feel fulfilled?
UTAGE NARRATION: The melancholy felt
by the most desired man.
UTAGE NARRATION: This is not sadness
from something lost...
UTAGE NARRATION: But the thirst of a king who wants
it all because he wants for nothing.
JUDGES: This doesn't fit with the song at all...
SIGN LEFT TO RIGHT: Producer
SIGN: Dance Expert
SIGN: Singing Expert
GIRLS: H-He's so cool!
YUINA: If Ouri-kun is a fleeting flower,
YUINA: then Tamon-kun is a diamond
that won't shatter for eternity!
RIKO: I know, right?
UTAGE: That needs to be in the textbooks!
SIGN: Instant crying!!
UTAGE: Exactly why are they
choosing another center?
SIGN: Current Ranking
SIGN: 2nd
SIGN: 3rd
SIGN: 4th
SIGN: 1st
SIGN: 5th
UTAGE: On that day, the followers of the
Church of Tamon realized something.
SIGN: m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
SIGN: Amon-tay @tamonuma2525
SIGN: Tamon-kun's visuals today are just too good again
SIGN: #FofF #TamonFukuharaSupportGroup
UTAGE: Tamon-kun's life completely
lacked the concept of heartbreak.
OURI: Tamon-kun, great job today!
TAMON: Y-You, too...
OURI: But man...
OURI: Even I didn't think you were
that much of a failure...
OURI: Only four battles remain.
Looks like I've got it in the bag.
OURI: I wonder what kind of look
OURI: that housekeeper girl has
on her face right about now.
OURI: Hopefully, she's not sick of you.
OURI: Well, see you tomorrow!
TAMON: It's over.
TAMON: I can't even fall in love with someone,
TAMON: so how am I even supposed to imagine
what heartbreak feels like?!
UTAGE: The room turned into a field of mushrooms.
TAMON: The harder I try, the more
I turn into Hottiehara.
TAMON: That's how I got by all this time,
and everyone's been happy with that.
TAMON: This incident made me realize my limit.
TAMON: In the end, that's all I can do.
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san...
MUSHROOMS: Gloomy, gloom.
UTAGE: Wait, what was that?! A mammoth?
UTAGE: Um... Gloomyhara-san, what's this sound?
OURI: Hey!
UTAGE: Oh, a gorilla.
OURI: Stop making this whole area so damn musty!
OURI: Now this crap's growing in my room, too!
TAMON: I'm so sorry!
UTAGE: You live upstairs?
OURI: Did you see that?
OURI: I showed how a center's meant to be!
UTAGE: Gloomyhara-san, I'm gonna
pick these mushrooms so I can vacuum.
OURI: Listen to me, damn it!
UTAGE: Well, the show just started, didn't it?
UTAGE: There are still plenty of chances
to turn this around.
OURI: We'll see about that.
OURI: All this one-trick idiot can do is
act like that gaudy host character!
UTAGE: The fact that he couldn't escape
the Hottiehara-kun character
UTAGE: is proof of just how hard
Gloomyhara-san's been working.
UTAGE: He's someone that can work hard.
UTAGE: Please don't call him an idiot.
OURI: Seriously, why?
OURI: All everyone ever talks about
is Tamon this, Tamon that!
OURI: This chick even knows what he's
really like, yet she stays by his side.
ADULT A: F/ACE's center is going to be
Sakaguchi-kun without a doubt!
ADULT B: He definitely inherited that
star DNA from his parents!
FAN A: Ouri-kun!
FAN B: Ouri-kun!
SIGN: A winner
before you were born
OURI: Look at me!
OURI: Hey, you!
OURI: If I become the center, come over to me!
UTAGE: Huh?
LYRICS: Uh huh...
LYRICS: Na na na...
LYRICS: I wonder what the world
would look like without you
LYRICS: When I look back,
you've always been by my side
LYRICS: Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
LYRICS: A speedboat sails across the endless skies
LYRICS: An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
LYRICS: An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
LYRICS: Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
LYRICS: Like a wilted flower coming back to life
LYRICS: A light that shines
LYRICS: Through the impossibly dark night
LYRICS: (Light of your soul)
LYRICS: I wanted to grasp it
LYRICS: (I love you so)
LYRICS: So I strived for it
LYRICS: Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
LYRICS: Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom